{
  "nickname": "자시니",
  "baseImage": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=5",
  "characterItems": {
    "face": {
      "id": "face_id_1",
      "showCase": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=1",
      "layoutCase": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=1"
    },
    "body": {
      "id": "body_id_1",
      "showCase": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=2",
      "layoutCase": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=2"
    },
    "expression": {
      "id": "expression_id_1",
      "showCase": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=3",
      "layoutCase": "https://picsum.photos/200/300?random=3"
    }
  },
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "저와 노는 방법은 ---이에요"
    }
  ],
  "myManualQAPair": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변1"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변2"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변3"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변4"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변5"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변6"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변7"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변8"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변9"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "저와 친해지는 방법은 ---이에요",
      "answer": "답변10"
    }
  ],
  "originKeywordPercents": {
    "키워드1": 1,
    "키워드2": 3,
    "키워드3": 5,
    "키워드4": 7,
    "키워드5": 9
  },
  "otherKeywordPercents": {
    "키워드1": 9,
    "키워드2": 7,
    "키워드3": 5,
    "키워드4": 3,
    "키워드5": 1
  }
}
